<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>[^BgTA^] - Raúl Romero García</title><link>https://www.bgta.net/</link><description>Recent content on [^BgTA^] - Raúl Romero García</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-EU</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.bgta.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://www.bgta.net/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.bgta.net/about/</guid><description>Passionate about new technologies, self-taught and restless mind. I have been in the computer world since I was 12 years old. I am currently a DevOps Engineer at Leadtech ;).
Open Source fan, GNU/Linux user from the 90’s and currently Ambassador of OpenSUSE in Spain.
I love programming and above all looking for solutions to problems in the developments. I do not hesitate to learn new programming languages if they are a good option for new projects or out of curiosity.</description></item><item><title>Gaming</title><link>https://www.bgta.net/gaming/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.bgta.net/gaming/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m not an expert gamer, but since I meet Google Stadia, I recovered my passion to play games like when I was a child.
Destiny 2 Destiny 2 (also known as Destiny 2: New Light) is a free-to-play online-only multiplayer first-person shooter video game developed by Bungie. It was originally released as a pay to play game in 2017 for PlayStation 4, Xbox One, and Microsoft Windows. It became free-to-play, utilizing the games as a service model, under the New Light title on October 1, 2019, followed by the game&amp;rsquo;s release on Stadia the following month, and then PlayStation 5 and Xbox Series X/S platforms in December 2020.</description></item><item><title>Music</title><link>https://www.bgta.net/music/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.bgta.net/music/</guid><description>I love listening music.
This is my recently listened music collage. Click over it!</description></item><item><title>iDEA: Declaración Electrónica de Accidente en tu Smartphone</title><link>https://www.bgta.net/posts/idea/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.bgta.net/posts/idea/</guid><description>Por desgracia, esta semana he sufrido un accidente de coche. Nada grave, ni tan solo fué culpa mía. Hacía muchos años que no tenía la necesidad de hacer un parte amistoso, pero gracias a la compañía que tengo actualmente, Helvetia descubrí que existe una aplicacción móvil que sirve para realizar los partes amistosos en caso de siniestro: App Declaración iDEA®.
La App Declaración iDEA® envía automáticamente el parte acordado entre los conductores implicados en un accidente, a las aseguradoras responsables de ambos vehículos.</description></item><item><title>Keybase.io: Verifica tu perfil, cifra tus ficheros y mensajes</title><link>https://www.bgta.net/posts/keybase/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.bgta.net/posts/keybase/</guid><description>Keybase.io está tratando de darle un aspecto social a toda la era del cifrado, para hacerlo más accesible a todo el mundo, y no solo me parece una gran idea, sino que me he enamorado de ella.
Keybase toma tú clave pública y la combina con tus redes sociales, para que puedas demostrar que eres quien dices ser.
Lo primero de todo es disponer de unas claves de cifrado PGP. Keybase nos ofrecerá la opción de crear una nueva o bien importar la que ya tengamos.</description></item></channel></rss>